<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>David Gorski&#x27;s Blog</title>
    <link href="https://blog.davidgorski.ca/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://blog.davidgorski.ca" />
    <updated>2023-09-23T13:29:55-04:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>David Gorski</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://blog.davidgorski.ca</id>

    <entry>
        <title>An Ode To Cities In The Rain</title>
        <author>
            <name>David Gorski</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://blog.davidgorski.ca/an-ode-to-cities-in-the-rain/"/>
        <id>https://blog.davidgorski.ca/an-ode-to-cities-in-the-rain/</id>

        <updated>2023-09-23T13:29:55-04:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Weather I am inside or outside, I love when it rains in cities. I call it ‘thinking weather’; but it is a lot more than that.</p>
<p>Ouside, the rain strips away the meanderers, frollikers and just-having-fun-ers. Which are of course by no means negative elements of the city. But leaving behind only the  ‘people with a reason to be out’, provides a type of locale clarity. People with un-skippable social events. Businesswomen on the way to important meetings. Tourists which desparately want to stick to their itineray. As I pass them on the sidewalks, I can’t help but feel a sense of elemental exposure camaraderie even as an joy-walking imposter.</p>
<p>Inside, the raindrops gathering on the windows absolve me of the guilt of not being ‘out’, a semi-permanent emotion metropolis residents have to deal with. “Why didn’t you check out that new art gallery?”; “It was raining!”. The weather outside makes me feel smaller, less significant, yet due to the paradox of <a href="https://www.newyorker.com/culture/culture-desk/the-year-of-hygge-the-danish-obsession-with-getting-cozy">Hygge</a>, I feel more empowered and more important indoors. The outside world needs to be less inviting; to make the home more inviting.</p>
<p>Every city is really three cities; a day city, a night city and a rain city. I am thankful anytime I get to experience a new city in the rain because that travel is much harder to plan. And <em>a city at night and in the rain</em>, well… let’s just say if I was writing about that the post wouldn’t end.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
